

BERTRAND HONNER

British & French **3** 02/03/1991

163 Rue Washington, 1050 Brussels, Belgium

✓ honnerbertrand@gmail.com

J +32 474 52 27 72

Junior Full-Stack Developer



linkedin.com/in/bertrandhonner



github.com/SuperchillB



codepen.io/SuperChillBertie

TECH SKILLS



LANGUAGE SKILLS

English (MT)			
French (MT)			
Spanish (C1-)			
German (B1+)			
Korean (B1-)			

PROJECTS/ **ACHIEVEMENTS**

DorothyCares.io (github link)

03/2018 - Present

Co-developed an AI platform designed to assist students throughout their experience at BeCode. In charge of redesigning and developing a front-end structure using vanilla JavaScript, Anime JS and GSAP, HTML5 and the latest CSS3 features. Also managed content creation using Dialogflow.

"Europe's Tech Big Four: KIC-Europe's Guide to the Continent's Top Startup Hubs"

08/2016 - 12/2016

Co-wrote a start-up guide specifically designed for stakeholders of the Korean startup ecosystem and distributed among Korean government entities

Housing Project India (Team Leader)

05/2012 - 08/2012

Built a school in a small village in Tamil Nadu, India. Led a team of 9 volunteers.

EXPERIENCE

11/2017 - 06/2018

Junior Full-Stack Developer

BeCode | Brussels, Belgium

A 7-month intensive web/mobile development bootcamp in Brussels with a strong focus on teamwork, personal development and new tech. Learned some of the most cutting edge front- and back-end development technologies. Also developed several projects, both independent and professional and took part in activities such as teaching code in schools and participating in Hackathons.

01/2016 - 12/2016

Project Manager

Korea Research & Innovation Centre – Europe | Brussels, Belgium

Coordinated the promotion of K-Startup Grand Challenge, Korea's largest accelerator programme for global start-ups, in Europe. Built and maintained networks with potential and existing partners invested within the startup ecosystems across Europe. Created promotional content and developed promotional tools for the programme. Scouted, selected and oversaw the pitching events of startups best fit for the programme. Delivered satisfying results in less than 3 months: the promotional campaign I was in charge of led to more than 900 start-up applications through our application platform.

10/2014 - 12/2015

Business Development Officer

Korea Research & Innovation Centre – Europe | Brussels, Belgium

Helped in the expansion of KIC-Europe's European network (innovation centres, start-up accelerators, R&D institutes, ...) through partnerships and event cooperation. Planned & successfully conducted two K-tech events. Conducted policy & innovation research for my thesis and also analysed EU R&D-related data and reported it back to the Korean government.

EDUCATION

2013 - 2015	Master of International Business & Management ICHEC Brussels, Belgium
2012 - 2013	International Exchange Program (Erasmus) Universidad Europea de Madrid Madrid, Spain
2010 - 2013	Bachelor of Business Administration
i	ICHEC Brussels, Belgium

HOBBIES / INTERESTS











Jazz musician

Photography

UI & coding

Languages

Traveling